Local 1199 Photograph Files 5933 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Bread and Roses (Box 84)
  - Bread and Roses - Urban Bush Women (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Bread and Roses visiting performers (A-G) (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Bread and Roses (visiting performers) (H-Z) (Box 84, Folder 23)
- Bread and Roses (Box 85)
  - Bread and Roses (visiting performers) - unidentified (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Bread and Roses (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Bread and Roses (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Bread and Roses (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Labor Day Street Fair, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Labor Day Street Fair - 1979 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Labor Day Street Fair - Sept. 1980 (1) (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Labor Day Street Fair #2 - Sept. 1, 1980 (2) (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Labor Day Street Fair #2, Sept. 1, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Labor Day Street Fair, 1982 - Miscellaneous (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Labor Day Street Fair, 1982 - Performers (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Labor Day Street Fair, 1982 - Bread and Roses (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Christmas Mag. Cover, 12/1971 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    13 slides
- Images digitized from the collection. (Box 86)